Capitol Hill History Club 094 094
Stage
Capitol Hill History Club Programs Collection
1920-1954
Stage
094
0.25 linear feet; 1 box
Biographical / Historical
This collection consists of materials found in the former home of Mr. Howard D. Woodson. They consist of personal materials from his time in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and materials from his time as superintendent of Sunday school at the Metropolitan A. M. E. Church in Washington, DC. Materials include, a commencement program, a tax levy, class lists, treasurer reports, monthly reports, annual reports, teaching aides, construction quotes and contracts, invoices, and speeches. The materials are arranged in alphabetical order by title or subject.
Custodial History
The programs were found in the collection, the source is unknown.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of 28 annual club programs.
Literature; Societies and clubs
- Series 1
  - No Subject of Study, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alaska, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The North American Indian, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Program, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Australasia, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Latin America, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Topics, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Early American History, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Expansion of the United States, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - History and Romance of the United States, 1792-1934, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - History in the Making, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - History in the Making, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glimpses of the Past and Present, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Constitution of the United States and the World Today, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Portraits and Personalities, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - History of the Arts and Sciences, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Latin America, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Latin America, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bringing the World to You, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A Glimpse of the World Today, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - History, Music, Drama, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The World of Today, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Review of Fifty Years, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Some Far Away Lands, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The World We Live In, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - World-Minded People, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Wider Horizons, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Wider Horizons, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)